So with that we're done!
What's the word for this, JoYCho TV!
Today, as you can probably tell if
you've seen us,
It's time for us to teach you guys,
English!
So for today we have our mainissiness,
Bambi!
Thank you!
I'm Rina and I'll be your English
teacher today.
Nice to meet you!
Are you guys okay?
Okay!
Today, we will do
SNS
self-introduction
in English.
Social network service.
First, there is a getchbook in front of
you.
Please write your name in English on
it.
When you understand, don't just say OK,
but also say I got it.
I got it.
Got it?
Ready?
It's okay.
Hi, I'm Leina from LA.
Currently, I'm living in Tokyo and
working in the entertainment business.
On my days off, I go boxing.
Oh, boxing!
Cool!
And my hashtag is
TokyoLeinaBambino from LA.
Okay?
Okay!
Oh, I see.
Do you understand?
Something like that.
TokyoLeinaBambino
Okay?
Yeah, go ahead.
My name is Hitoka Sakai.
I like tomatoes.
My hobby is singing and dancing.
Dancing?
Dancing.
I have a dog.
My name is Leo.
I'm a model and an idol.
Hashtag people, hashtag model, hashtag
idol, hashtag Leo.
Okay?
Yeah!
Good!
I think I spelled it wrong.
But I think that's like...
75 likes.
75 likes?
That's pretty good, isn't it?
It's good, it's good.
Yeah.
Okay, is that okay?
Okay, name.
Eh?
This is Neme. What's Neme, right?
I like eating.
You like eating, right?
So, eating.
Okay, eating tomato.
My top 3 is...
I have 2 Bs.
What's the first one?
Sing.
I like singing.
Singing.
Okay.
Fail.
Perfect.
Thank you.
Hello.
My name is Bambi Fujimoto.
My hobby is reading books.
My favorite food is...
And the last one is...
Hashtag Bambi.
Hashtag my hobby.
Hashtag my favorite food.
Hashtag heart!
Bambi, yours is good, but you're moving
so much.
Right? It's okay, it's okay.
Good job! I think that's like...
40 likes?
Wait a minute!
Wait, wait, can you compare this to me?
Isn't this crazy?
This is crazy! I'm scared!
My ears are turning red!
This is crazy!
I'm scared!
40 likes!
I'm so embarrassed!
Thank you!
It's cute!
It's like... maybe like...
60 likes?
It's okay! It's okay!
Cute, cute!
It's like... dogs?
My pet's name?
Name, name, name!
My pet bear is...
It's a bear, right?
Yeah, I'm not sure. Is it a bear?
No bear, right?
Dog?
Dog, okay.
My pet's name...
With this, my pet's name is...
Pet's name is...
Him! Not bad?
Not bad! Good job!
Thank you!
Very cute!
My name is Haruka Koizumi. I like
ramen. I play the guitar. Nice to meet
you!
Hashtag Oharu. Hashtag Tokimichi Pink.
Hashtag I love guitar and music. Hashtag
Ramen Big Love Koizumi.
Thank you!
It's good, it's good. Maybe like...
I think like 70 likes.
Around 70 likes.
I think it's good to be specific.
Can I fix now?
Nice to meet you.
Oh, it's different.
Nice to meet...
Meet...
Thank you for watching.
You understand?
I hope so.
Ramen, big love.
Ice cream, big love.
I love ramen.
It's okay.
I'm Julia.
My favorite food is ice cream.
I'm 15 years old.
I love Japan, Tokyo, and ice cream.
We're going to use the hashtag, cute,
hashtag, guard, hashtag, high school
student, high school student.
Finish!
That was perfect.
I think that's like,
the year of the pig.
Oh, that was really good!
Looks perfect.
Wow!
I think the hashtag was really good.
My name is Hiyori Yoshikawa.
My member card is Tokimeki Green.
From Tokimeki Sendenbu.
Hashtag Tokisen.
Hashtag Hiyori Green.
Hashtag...
So fine
Boiled duck ranch
Book
Ok, good
I like your energy
Good energy
You're welcome, I'm gonna change it
That was dope!
Mene.
Name.
Same as Yoshitaka.
A little different.
Yoshitaka is the first to come.
Mene.
Name.
I see.
I'm embarrassed.
Yoshitaka is...
Yes.
My member color.
I don't know.
It's a little different.
A little different?
It's okay, right?
Was green difficult?
It's green.
Green?
I'm going to have a hard time with my
Japanese.
I have no Japanese.
The color is green.
Okay?
From Toki...
From?
From Tokimeki Senden...
Thank you for watching!
You're so good at it!
You're gross, right?
You're cute, right?
It's hard to be with you.
I think...
Even if you say katakana in English...
Right?
You can still convey passion.
Oh, I see.
I see.
Let's do our best.
I think maybe...
I'm an idol.
I want to tell them that I'm an idol.
A is a hashtag that is popular in
America.
A hashtag that is popular overseas.
There are some hashtags that are
popular or are used all the time.
What?
I've never seen it.
I've never seen OOTD.
It's a pretty standard.
It's a trend now, or it's a trend all
the time.
What is OOTD?
I don't know.
TBT is Throwback Thursday.
Throwback Thursday, this FBF world.
It's a shame, but it's FBF.
This is for example,
when you want to upload a nostalgic
photo,
you use this.
It's a photo from before, but it's
called throwback.
It's called throwback.
When you upload a photo from before,
everyone uses this.
FBF is FBF Thursday.
What does OOTD mean?
It's Thursday.
Oh, good!
I know what it means.
Outfit of the day.
what is the outfit of the day?
the one with the hat
yeah the one with the hat
OOT
like a costume?
like a costume or a dress?
the outfit
so
what is OOTN?
what is it?
close close, just this part is
different
just this part is different
What is it?
Night?
Night is correct
Today?
It's like a night out
For lunch, you wear a lap top and a
uniform
For dinner, you wear a fancy outfit
And then you wear this
Wow
I don't know if it's a day or night
I don't know
It's a day
What do you guys want to do in English?
What do you want to upload and what do
you want to do in Japanese?
I like matcha
What is Tokimeku in English?
I love matcha
I love green tea
Green tea?
Are you Japanese?
Japanese is matcha
No, no, no
You are Japanese?
Ok, so you love green tea too
I do too, ok?
Ok
What is Tokimeku in English?
I love green tea
Spark?
Spark Joy?
Spark Joy is popular overseas.
Wow!
Do you know Konmari?
Konmari method is...
You know?
You clean up!
Yes, yes, yes.
So, this is Tokimeku.
Tokimeku.
So, everyone is saying Spark Joy, Spark
Joy.
So, let's get on it.
Get on it?
So, everyone...
We have to wear this.
Live?
We...
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to our channel!
I'll do it, so come to me.
OK.
Wait, wait.
I can't do it.
I've already done it before.
Really?
From there?
C, C, C.
C?
It's normal.
Only B is too big.
December 21st in Nakano Sun Plaza, we
will have a concert!
Yeah!
Yeah, good for me!
I'm gonna change, okay? A little bit.
On December 21st.
Like, everyone come see us.
Okay, okay!
If you're ever in Sydney, please come
see us!
Okay!
Ready?
I'll say it first, so you repeat after
me.
Okay!
Locking on your heart.
Good! We are Tokimeki Sendenbu.
We are Tokimeki Sendenbu.
On December 21st,
We will have a concert
In Nakano San Fraso
Please come see us!
Okay!
Now, I think you learned a lot,
so please write a self-introduction
so that you can feel new.
Okay!
Finally, I'll make a statement.
My specialty is impromptu streaming and
advertising.
I'm really good at improv.
Improv.
Improv is a shorter version.
Improvisation is a longer version.
Improvising.
You make a song on the spot.
That's right.
I'm really good at making songs on the
spot.
On the spot.
You make a song on the spot.
Good at making songs.
This is easier to remember.
I'm good at making songs.
It's longer.
I'm really
Really
Good
at making songs.
Songs.
All therough so high and whole space.
Ok now for Kiri-chan.
Can you make a Fukuta-pub by J-5?
Did you sing yet?
Yes need to be adjusted a little here.
Are you ready?
Yay! That's exciting!
Hitoka, can you please read?
Yeah, go ahead.
You?
Hello.
My name is Hitoka Sakai.
I like eating tomatoes.
My hobby is singing and dancing.
I have a dog.
My dog's name is Leo.
I'm a model and I'm also a member of
Tokimeki Promotion Club.
Please remember me as the head of the
group.
Hashtag Hitoka, hashtag idol, hashtag
model, hashtag Leo, hashtag SparkJoy,
hashtag Tokimeki, hashtag follow me.
Thank you.
I'm a model and I'm also a member of
Tokimeki Promotion Club.
You did a great job!
I love french fries!
I'm a member of Tokimeki Senden.
My member card is lemon.
Please remember me as a member of the
group.
Nice to meet you!
I love french fries!
Very good!
Next, Kaname!
Hello!
My name is Kanami Tsujino. I'm from
Japan. I like dogs. My pet name is Kuma.
My favorite food is cookies. I'm an
idol.
I'm a member of Tokimeki Sendai. Please
remember me as a member of the group on
December 25th.
We will have a concert in Nakano-san
Plaza. Please come see us!
Hashtag SparkJoy, hashtag Tokimeki,
hashtag Japan, hashtag follow me,
hashtag idol!
Ok, next up, Haruka!
Hello! My name is Haruka Koizumi. I'm a
member of Tokimeki Sendai.
Please remember me as a member of the
group on December 25th.
Think of the group.
I like eating.
My favorite food is ramen.
I like music.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Please tell your friends about us. Nice
to meet you!
Hashtag Haruka, hashtag pink, hashtag
idol, hashtag Japan, hashtag staff join,
hashtag tukimeki, hashtag follow me,
hashtag I love guitar and music, hashtag
I love ramen.
By Koizumi-san!
Good! Very good!
Okay, next is Julia.
Hello, I'm Julia. I'm a singer.
I'm...
Hello, I'm Julia An.
I'm 15 years old.
My favorite food is ice cream.
I'm a member of the SNS.
My member color is purple.
Please remember me as a purple of the
group.
Please tell your friends about us.
Thank you!
Hashtag Japan, hashtag Tokyo, hashtag
ice cream.
Hashtag cute, hashtag girl, hashtag
high school student, hashtag Tokite,
hashtag spark joy, hashtag tokimeki,
hashtag I'm an idol, hashtag selfie,
hashtag follow me, hashtag follow for a
full moon, hashtag like for life!
Yay!
Good, good, very good!
Alright, Hiroki, you're singing, right?
Singing, awesome!
Yes!
Good job!
Music, start!
I am a member of Doki Doki Doki Doki
Doki Sendenbu
My name is Hiyori Yoshikawa
Please remember me as the queen of the
group
I'm really, really good at making some
other spots
On December 21st, we will have a
concert in Nakano, Sapporo
Please come and see us
Please tell your friends about us
Hashtag Tokisen, hashtag SparkJoy,
hashtag I'm an idol
I'm a diver, guarantee
Follow me
Oh yeah
Thank you!
That was really good.
Well, your sign just now was fake.
We made a mistake.
Very good, very good.
So please keep this in mind.
It's like art.
Got it?
Got it.
Good job today very good!
Everyone stand up
Thank you!
Thank you very much.
I am confident that I can satisfy my
fans.
I can definitely surpass them.
I will record my voice forever.
I will make you satisfied.
This is the last show of the year, so I
think the excitement is the best in the
year.
This is a big and important show for me
that I can't end this year without it.
I think it's a show that everyone can
connect and have one thought.
I've been working hard for this year to
make this show a success, so I want a
lot of people to come and it's a really
important show for us.
I want to make it a success this year.
I want to make it a good show for
everyone.
I'm looking forward to it.
I want to see the old Toki-san of
Iwamura, but I think the Toki-san now is
the brightest.
I want you to see us in person.
If you want to come, I want you to come
to the Nakano Satsuma.
If you want to come to the legendary
live, I want you to come.
I want you to come to the Toki-san
live.
I want you to come.
Next episode
Please subscribe to my channel!